<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CoinSimple</title>
    <description>Full Bitcoin e-Commerce, Direct to your Wallet</description>
    <link>https://coinsimple.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://coinsimple.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 12:53:43 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 12:53:43 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Will CoinSimple integrate PayPal or Stripe payments?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We at CoinSimple believe that the future of payments is decentralized and peer-to-peer. We also believe that the centralized payment processor space is well served, and increasingly crowded. Because of that we have decided to focus on developing products solely for the cryptocurrency space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are your options if you are a merchant and want to provide both a decentralized solution (CoinSimple) and a centralized solution like PayPal or Stripe? There are several options but the one that we have found easiest to work with are a combination of Wordpress for your e-commerce store, WooCommerce for the centralized payments, and the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/coinsimple/coinsimple-woocommerce&quot;&gt;CoinSimple WooCommerce plugin&lt;/a&gt; for the decentralized solutions. See a demo of such a set up, without the PayPal integration, &lt;a href=&quot;http://woocommerce.coinsimple.com&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2015 10:21:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>https://coinsimple.com/faq/will-coinsimple-integrate-paypal-or-stripe-payments</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://coinsimple.com/faq/will-coinsimple-integrate-paypal-or-stripe-payments</guid>
        
        
        <category>faq</category>
        
        <category>coinsimple basics</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How can I use CoinSimple with my Website or Email Newsletter?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This guide explains how to create a button or link on your website, or on your email newsletter, so that you can sell your products and services using CoinSimple. This approach is most useful if you have an HTML-based website or email newsletter; If your website runs on Magento, Wordpress eCommerce, or WooCommerce, please read the relevant articles for more detailed instructions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: If your website runs Magento, WooCommerce or Wordpress eCommerce, please read the following support articles for &lt;a href=&quot;http://coinsimple.com/how-can-i-use-coinsimple-with-magento&quot;&gt;Magento&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://coinsimple.com/how-can-i-use-coinsimple-with-woocommerce&quot;&gt;WooCommerce&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://coinsimple.com/how-can-i-use-coinsimple-with-wordpress-ecommerce&quot;&gt;Wordpress eCommerce&lt;/a&gt;, respectively.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is very easy to sell your products and services online through CoinSimple. Even if you don’t have a website that runs specialized eCommerce software, with CoinSimple you can create a link or a button that will allow your customers to pay you in bitcoin. As usual, your bitcoin will end up in your wallet (Electrum, Armory, Trezor or any other bitcoin address), bitcoin processor account (BitPay, Coinbase, GoCoin), or bitcoin exchange, with CoinSimple “doing all the work” and without ever touching any of your bitcoins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to do that, you need to create a “Button” by going to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://app.coinsimple.com/&quot;&gt;CoinSimple web application&lt;/a&gt; and clicking on “Buttons”. The process is very similar to that for creating an invoice using CoinSimple and sending it via email, see &lt;a href=&quot;http://coinsimple.com/support/how-can-i-use-coinsimple-to-issue-invoices-and-send-them-via-email&quot;&gt;detailed instructions here&lt;/a&gt;) with a few differences:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;When you create a button you do not need to enter the name and email of you customer. That information will be filled by your customer the moment they click on your website’s button.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;You need to specify a webpage where the user will be sent (“redirected”) after they make a payment. Think of this page as the “&lt;em&gt;Thank you, your order is being processed&lt;/em&gt;” page that eCommerce stores have. You should create such a page on your website for your customers. This is the “Redirect URI” that you will see on the form for creating a button on CoinSimple.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;If your website can receive notifications for payments, you can enter the “Callback URI” on the form for creating a button on CoinSimple. That way your website will know that a payment is made, and it could potentially make a page available to a certain user. If you have a simple website or a newsletter, and you don’t have the ability to modify your pages based on notifications, you can leave the “Callback URI” empty. Just make sure that you check your email or CoinSimple dashboard to find out if a customer has paid, so that you can ship your product.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With CoinSimple, websites of any complexity can be easily set up to accept bitcoin. Please use this feature and let us know what you think on &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/coinsimple&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; or at &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#115;&amp;#117;&amp;#112;&amp;#112;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#116;&amp;#064;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#105;&amp;#110;&amp;#115;&amp;#105;&amp;#109;&amp;#112;&amp;#108;&amp;#101;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#109;&quot;&gt;&amp;#115;&amp;#117;&amp;#112;&amp;#112;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#116;&amp;#064;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#105;&amp;#110;&amp;#115;&amp;#105;&amp;#109;&amp;#112;&amp;#108;&amp;#101;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#109;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2015 09:49:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>https://coinsimple.com/support/how-can-i-use-coinsimple-with-my-website-or-email-newsletter</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://coinsimple.com/support/how-can-i-use-coinsimple-with-my-website-or-email-newsletter</guid>
        
        
        <category>support</category>
        
        <category>bitcoin for ecommerce merchants</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How can I use CoinSimple with Magento?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The CoinSimple Magento plugin allows e-commerce stores to accept bitcoin through CoinSimple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;requirements&quot;&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Business ID and API key from CoinSimple.com&lt;/strong&gt;. To find your information, go to your &lt;a href=&quot;http://coinsimple.com&quot;&gt;CoinSimple.com&lt;/a&gt; dashboard, select your business, and go to “Settings”. You will find your &lt;em&gt;Business ID&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;API key&lt;/em&gt; under “Busines Information” and “API Credentials”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;installation&quot;&gt;Installation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are two ways to install this plugin. (1) Through the “Magento Connect Manager” or (2) by uploading a file directly to your Magento server.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;option-1-install-using-the-magento-connect-manager&quot;&gt;Option 1: Install using the “Magento Connect Manager”&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/coinsimple/coinsimple-magento/releases/download/v1/CoinSimple-1.0.0.tgz&quot;&gt;Download the specially formatted .tgz file of the plugin&lt;/a&gt; to a location of your choice.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Log in to your Magento site as administrator and click on “Settings” and then “Magento Connect” and “Magento Connect Manager”.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/plugins/magento/magento-plugin-magento_connect.png&quot; alt=&quot;Select &amp;quot;Settings&amp;quot; and then &amp;quot;Magento Connect&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Magento Connect Manager&amp;quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Login again, using the administrator user name and password.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;If not already selected, select the “Extensions” tab and go to the “Direct package upload” section of the page&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/plugins/magento/magento-plugin-magento_connect-upload.png&quot; alt=&quot;&amp;quot;Direct package upload&amp;quot; section of the page&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Choose the file that you downloaded in the first step, and click “Upload”. Magento Connect will import the file and show you the following screen.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/plugins/magento/magento-plugin-magento_connect-upload_confirmation.png&quot; alt=&quot;Successful installation of the CoinSimple plugin for Magento&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;option-2-install-by-uploading-a-file-to-your-magento-server&quot;&gt;Option 2: Install by uploading a file to your Magento server.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/coinsimple/coinsimple-magento/archive/v1.zip&quot;&gt;Download the zip file of the plugin&lt;/a&gt;. Extract the zip file.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Copy the contents of the zip file under in the root of your Magento installation, usually &lt;code&gt;htdocs&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this point the plugin is installed and activated but it still needs to be enabled and configured.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;configuration&quot;&gt;Configuration&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Log in to your Magento site as administrator and click on “Settings” and then “Configuration”.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/plugins/magento/magento-plugin-settings-configuration.png&quot; alt=&quot;Select &amp;quot;Settings&amp;quot; and then &amp;quot;Configuration&amp;quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;In the screen that appears click on “Payment Methods” on the left.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/plugins/magento/magento-plugin-settings-configuration-payment_methods.png&quot; alt=&quot;Click on &amp;quot;Payment Methods&amp;quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Select “Yes” in the “Enabled” dropdown menu and enter your CoinSimple.com business ID and CoinSimple API key in the appropriate fields. Also, enter the URL of the page that your customers will be directed to after they make their payment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/plugins/magento/magento-plugin-settings-configuration-payment_methods-coinsimple.png&quot; alt=&quot;Business ID, API key and callback URL&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Click “Save Config”.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;use&quot;&gt;Use&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;When a buyer selects “Bitcoin” as their payment method, an invoice is generated at CoinSimple.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;After the buyer pays, CoinSimple directs the buyer to the page that you selected in your Settings above.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;support&quot;&gt;Support&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;coinsimple-support&quot;&gt;CoinSimple Support&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If you are having a problem with this plugin, please use &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/coinsimple/coinsimple-magento/issues&quot;&gt;this Github issues page&lt;/a&gt; to report your problem.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;magento-support&quot;&gt;Magento Support&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://magento.com&quot;&gt;Homepage&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://docs.magentocommerce.com&quot;&gt;Documentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.magentocommerce.com/support/ce/&quot;&gt;Community Edition Support Forums&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;troubleshooting&quot;&gt;Troubleshooting&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;This plugin requires PHP 5.4 or higher to function correctly. Contact your webhosting provider or server administrator if you are unsure which version is installed on your web server.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ensure a valid SSL certificate is installed on your server. Also ensure your root CA cert is updated. If your CA cert is not current, you will see curl SSL verification errors.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Verify that your web server is not blocking POSTs from servers it may not recognize. Double check this on your firewall as well, if one is being used.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Check the system error log file (usually the web server error log) for any errors during CoinSimple payment attempts. If you contact CoinSimple support, they will ask to see the log file to help diagnose the problem.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If all else fails, send an email describing your issue in detail to &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#115;&amp;#117;&amp;#112;&amp;#112;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#116;&amp;#064;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#105;&amp;#110;&amp;#115;&amp;#105;&amp;#109;&amp;#112;&amp;#108;&amp;#101;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#109;&quot;&gt;&amp;#115;&amp;#117;&amp;#112;&amp;#112;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#116;&amp;#064;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#105;&amp;#110;&amp;#115;&amp;#105;&amp;#109;&amp;#112;&amp;#108;&amp;#101;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#109;&lt;/a&gt;. In your support request, please provide:
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Magento version&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;PHP version&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Other plugins installed&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Configuration settings for the CoinSimple plugin&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Screenshot of error messages, if any&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2015 11:47:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>https://coinsimple.com/support/how-can-i-use-coinsimple-with-magento</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://coinsimple.com/support/how-can-i-use-coinsimple-with-magento</guid>
        
        
        <category>support</category>
        
        <category>bitcoin for ecommerce merchants</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How can I accept bitcoin directly to a bitcoin address using CoinSimple?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;You can use CoinSimple to accept bitcoins directly to any bitcoin address. This guide shows you how to find your bitcoin address in several wallets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;example-wallets&quot;&gt;Example Wallets&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#bitcoin-core&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Core&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#multibit&quot;&gt;MultiBit&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#hive&quot;&gt;Hive&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#green-address&quot;&gt;Green Address&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#blockchaininfo&quot;&gt;Blockchain.info&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a id=&quot;bitcoin-core&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;bitcoin-core&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Core&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Start Bitcoin Core and click on the “File” menu and the on “Receiving Addresses”.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Select the address that you would like to use and click on the “Copy” button on the lower left.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Return to the CoinSimple website and paste the bitcoin address.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#example-wallets&quot;&gt;Back To Top&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a id=&quot;multibit&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;multibit&quot;&gt;Multibit&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Start MultiBit and click on the “Trade” menu and the on “Request Bitcoin”.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;On the right panel, you will see a Bitcoin address. Press on the button that is right next to the address to copy it to your clipboard.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Return to the CoinSimple website and paste the bitcoin address.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#example-wallets&quot;&gt;Back To Top&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;hive&quot;&gt;Hive&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Start Hive and hover your mouse over the Bitcoin address of your choice.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Click on the address and it will be copied to your clipboard.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Return to the CoinSimple website and paste the bitcoin address.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#example-wallets&quot;&gt;Back To Top&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;green-address&quot;&gt;Green Address&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Start Green Address and click on “Receive Money” link on the left.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Click on “Show URI and address”.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Select the bitcoin address that starts with either 1 or 3 and copy it.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Return to the CoinSimple website and paste the bitcoin address.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#example-wallets&quot;&gt;Back To Top&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;blockchaininfo&quot;&gt;Blockchain.info&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Login to Blockchain.info.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;On the lower left of the screen, you will see a box that says “This Is Your Bitcoin Address”. Copy the address to your clipboard.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Return to the CoinSimple website and paste the bitcoin address.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#example-wallets&quot;&gt;Back To Top&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 19:05:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>https://coinsimple.com/support/how-can-i-accept-bitcoin-directly-to-a-bitcoin-address-using-coinsimple</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://coinsimple.com/support/how-can-i-accept-bitcoin-directly-to-a-bitcoin-address-using-coinsimple</guid>
        
        
        <category>support</category>
        
        <category>using coinsimple</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How can I connect my BitPay account with CoinSimple?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;In order to use CoinSimple to integrate with the BitPay bitcoin payment processor, you need to pair your BitPay account with CoinSimple. This guide explains how to do that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please follow these steps:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 1&lt;/strong&gt;: Login to your BitPay account and click on the menu link in the upper left part of your screen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 2&lt;/strong&gt;: Click on ‘Settings’.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wallets/bitpay/bitpay-action-1-settings.png&quot; alt=&quot;Login to your BitPay account and click on the menu link in the upper left part of your screen. Click on &#39;Settings&#39;.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;reference&quot;&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;BitPay Menu: Settings&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Login to your BitPay account and click on the menu link in the upper left part of your screen. Click on &#39;Settings&#39;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 3&lt;/strong&gt;: Scroll down the menu until you find the ‘Developer Resources’ subsection of the Settings menu. Click on ‘API Tokens’.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wallets/bitpay/bitpay-action-2-api_tokens.png&quot; alt=&quot;Scroll down the menu until you find the &#39;Developer Resources&#39; subsection of the Settings menu. Click on &#39;API Tokens&#39;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;reference&quot;&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;BitPay Menu: API Tokens&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scroll down the menu until you find the &#39;Developer Resources&#39; subsection of the Settings menu. Click on &#39;API Tokens&#39;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 4&lt;/strong&gt;: Click on ‘Add New Token’.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wallets/bitpay/bitpay-form-add_new_token.png&quot; alt=&quot;Click on &#39;Add Token&#39;.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;reference&quot;&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;BitPay Menu: Add New Token&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click on &#39;Add New Token&#39;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 5&lt;/strong&gt;: In the ‘Token Label’ field enter a name for your token, for example ‘CoinSimple’ and press ‘Add Token’.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wallets/bitpay/bitpay-action-3-add_token.png&quot; alt=&quot;In the &#39;Token Label&#39; field enter a name for your token, for example &#39;CoinSimple&#39; and press &#39;Add Token&#39;.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;reference&quot;&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;BitPay Form: Add Token&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the &#39;Token Label&#39; field enter a name for your token, for example &#39;CoinSimple&#39; and press &#39;Add Token&#39;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 6&lt;/strong&gt;: Copy the ‘Pairing Code’ shown and copy it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/img/wallets/bitpay/bitpay-token.png&quot; alt=&quot;Copy the &#39;Pairing Code&#39; shown and copy it.&quot; /&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;reference&quot;&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;BitPay Pairing Code&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Copy the &#39;Pairing Code&#39; shown and copy it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 7&lt;/strong&gt;: Go to the CoinSimple website, navigate to “Settings”, “Wallets and Processors”, and click on “BitPay”. In the form that appears, paste the copied pairing code.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 8&lt;/strong&gt;: Click “Submit”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 9&lt;/strong&gt;: You will need to verify the addition of your BitPay account. So, check your email for a message from CoinSimple and click on the relevant link.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Congratulations! You can now start receiving bitcoin directly to the BitPay account.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 17:52:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>https://coinsimple.com/support/how-can-i-connect-my-bitpay-account-with-coinsimple</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://coinsimple.com/support/how-can-i-connect-my-bitpay-account-with-coinsimple</guid>
        
        
        <category>support</category>
        
        <category>using coinsimple</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How can I connect my GoCoin account with CoinSimple?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;In order to connect your GoCoin account with CoinSimple, you need to allow the CoinSimple application that we have set up at GoCoin.com to create invoices on your behalf. The process is interactive and it starts as soon as you press the “Connect” button for the GoCoin payment processor on the CoinSimple settings page.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2015 12:07:24 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>https://coinsimple.com/support/how-can-i-connect-my-gocoin-account-with-coinsimple</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://coinsimple.com/support/how-can-i-connect-my-gocoin-account-with-coinsimple</guid>
        
        
        <category>support</category>
        
        <category>using coinsimple</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How can I connect my Coinbase account with CoinSimple?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;In order to connect your Coinbase account with CoinSimple, you need to allow the CoinSimple application that we have set up at Coinbase.com to create invoices on your behalf. The process is interactive and it starts as soon as you press the “Connect” button for the Coinbase payment processor on the CoinSimple settings page.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2015 12:07:24 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>https://coinsimple.com/support/how-can-i-connect-my-coinbase-account-with-coinsimple</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://coinsimple.com/support/how-can-i-connect-my-coinbase-account-with-coinsimple</guid>
        
        
        <category>support</category>
        
        <category>using coinsimple</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How can I connect my BitPay account with CoinSimple using BitPay&#39;s legacy API keys?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;In order to use CoinSimple to integrate with the BitPay bitcoin payment processor, you need to copy your BitPay API key on your BitPay dashboard and enter it in CoinSimple. This guide explains how to do that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please follow these steps:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Go to &lt;a href=&quot;http://bitpay.com&quot;&gt;bitpay.com&lt;/a&gt; and sign in.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Go to &lt;a href=&quot;http://bitpay.com/api-keys&quot;&gt;bitpay.com/api-keys&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Click on the “Add New API Key” button.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;(Optional) Click on the “Edit” button and in the memo field add the description “CoinSimple”.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Copy the “API Key ID”, that is a series of characters and numbers like gO0HWTAT9v3UJVP89kQNO2ZSpmmZcUzukr6EeuskER1.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Return to the BitPay page on the CoinSimple website. Paste the copied the key in the “API Key ID” field. Press “Submit”.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Congratulations! You can now start receiving bitcoin through BitPay, no developer was necessary.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2015 12:07:24 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>https://coinsimple.com/support/how-can-i-connect-my-bitpay-account-with-coinsimple-using-legacy-api-keys</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://coinsimple.com/support/how-can-i-connect-my-bitpay-account-with-coinsimple-using-legacy-api-keys</guid>
        
        
        <category>support</category>
        
        <category>using coinsimple</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>CoinSimple and MeXBT working to integrate their platforms</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Miami, January 17, 2015&lt;/strong&gt;: Hong Kong-based e-commerce platform CoinSimple and meXBT, one of Latin America’s leading Bitcoin exchanges will integrate to give their customers the best of both worlds. On behalf of the two Seedcoin-backed startups, CoinSimple Founder and CEO Nikos Bentenitis and meXBT Founder and CEO Gabriel Miron announced the news today during The North American Bitcoin Conference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Under the agreement, CoinSimple clients will be able to use meXBT’s bitcoin prices and exchange services, and meXBT clients will be able to create fully functioning CoinSimple accounts in a few clicks. Furthermore, the MeXBT-CoinSimple integration will allow customers of meXBT to use the CoinSimple web app to issue invoices for services; the CoinSimple Wordpress eCommerce, WooCommerce and Magento plugins to sell products through their online stores; and the “Pay in Bitcoin” buttons on any web page to accept donations or even sell individual products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We are looking forward to working with CoinSimple to expand our merchant offerings in Latin America, and to continue driving bitcoin adoption in the region”, said Miron.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We are excited to partner with meXBT and expand our services and white-label merchant processing to Mexico and Latin America,” said Bentenitis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About meXBT.com&lt;/strong&gt;: Providing digital currencies for serious traders and simple enough for beginners, meXBT’s goal is to provide the best and most secure service to traders of digital currencies. meXBT is combining state-of-the-art technology with a rock solid legal and fiscal structure on a single platform called meXBT.com, the ‘Crypto Exchange of the Americas’ and the place to be when exchanging cryptos. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mexbt.com&quot;&gt;www.mexbt.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About CoinSimple&lt;/strong&gt;: CoinSimple provides “Full Bitcoin e-Commerce, Direct to Wallet”. “Full Bitcoin e-Commerce” because it provides sophisticated merchant processing that includes multiple currencies, customer analytics, unique bitcoin addresses per transaction, accounting, invoices, email notifications and plugins for e-Commerce platforms (Wordpress, WooCommerce, Magento etc.) “Direct to wallet” because it allows full control of funds, privacy, deterministic wallets, choice of price source, ability to convert bitcoin at the exchange of choice. For more information about CoinSimple, please contact us at &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#109;&amp;#101;&amp;#100;&amp;#105;&amp;#097;&amp;#064;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#105;&amp;#110;&amp;#115;&amp;#105;&amp;#109;&amp;#112;&amp;#108;&amp;#101;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#109;&quot;&gt;&amp;#109;&amp;#101;&amp;#100;&amp;#105;&amp;#097;&amp;#064;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#105;&amp;#110;&amp;#115;&amp;#105;&amp;#109;&amp;#112;&amp;#108;&amp;#101;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#109;&lt;/a&gt; or visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://coinsimple.com&quot;&gt;CoinSimple.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Seedcoin&lt;/strong&gt;: Seedcoin is the world’s first seed-stage Bitcoin startup virtual incubator. Seedcoin’s objective is to invest in the creative entrepreneurs of the cryptocurrency and blockchain economy and help them develop the future services, products and applications re-shaping the way we interact with money on a daily basis. Visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.seedco.in&quot;&gt;www.seedco.in&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2015 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>https://coinsimple.com/blog/coinsimple-and-mexbt-partner-to-integrate-their-platforms</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://coinsimple.com/blog/coinsimple-and-mexbt-partner-to-integrate-their-platforms</guid>
        
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
        <category>press release</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How can I use CoinSimple to issue invoices and send them via email?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This guide explains how to issue your first CoinSimple invoice, in 2 steps. The process is quite simple but the steps are described here in great detail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you haven’t already done so, set up an account with CoinSimple. Detailed instructions on how to do that, can be found &lt;a href=&quot;http://coinsimple.com/support/how-can-i-set-up-an-account-with-coinsimple&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;create-an-invoice&quot;&gt;1. Create an invoice&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All you have to do is click on “Invoices” and then on “New Invoice”. At that point you need to enter or choose:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You client’s name&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Your client’s email&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The currency that you want to price your invoice in (all national currencies are supported)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The wallet or payment processor that you want to receive your funds to&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The source of bitcoin price (Bitcoin Average, CoinDesk, Blockchain.info, Bitstamp, BitPay, Coinbase, GoCoin) or a set price&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The name of your invoice items, their numbers and their unit price&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can also, optionally, choose a discount or to make your invoice &lt;em&gt;recurring&lt;/em&gt;, on the same day of every month, or every a certain number of days. Recurring invoices will be sent perpetually, or for a certain number of times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;save-the-invoice-and-select-delivery-options&quot;&gt;2. Save the invoice and select delivery options&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this point, you can send your invoice via email, review it, edit it, or delete it.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2015 17:57:24 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>https://coinsimple.com/support/how-can-i-use-coinsimple-to-issue-invoices-and-send-them-via-email</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://coinsimple.com/support/how-can-i-use-coinsimple-to-issue-invoices-and-send-them-via-email</guid>
        
        
        <category>support</category>
        
        <category>using coinsimple</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
